Guide to the James Lockhart Autry Family Papers, 1832-1998 MS 003
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Texas, 1875-1998, 148143
  - James Lockhart Autry II, 1859-1920; 148151
    - Sub-Series I: Numbered Files, 1861-1920, 869
      - Concerning Mr. Autry's Health [883], 1919-1920; 952 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Trust Agreement-Eureka Paving Co. [886], 1916; 949 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Washington Apartments [887], 1916; 948 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Maid-Applications and Letters Concerning Employment [888], 1916; 947 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - American Republics Corp.-Sale of 3400 Shares [889], 1916; 946 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - List of Names of Probable Investors - American Republics Corporation [890], 1916; 945 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Bankers Trust Company [891], 1916; 944 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - New York Stock Exchange Requirements [892], 1916; 943 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Texas State Historical Association [835 + 893], 1916; 942 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Texas State Historical Association [893], 148832 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Concerning a List of Investors [894], 1916; 941 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Tidewater Oil Company [895], 1916; 940 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Boat Landing [896], 1916; 939 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - G.L. Cash Claim-Wheeler and Pickens Subdivision [897], 1916; 938 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Houston Art league [898], 1916; 937 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Mrs. Huberta R. Nunn [899], 1916-1919; 936 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Houston Oil Company Suits [900], 1914-1919; 935 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Christ Episcopal Church-Finance, etc. [901], 1912-1920; 934 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - M.M. White Land notes [902], 1913-1915; 933 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Jasper Riles - Land Notes [903], 1915; 932 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Summer Trip [904], 1917; 931 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - Men's Club of Christ Episcopal Church [906], 1916; 930 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Marshall Field & Company [909], 1916-1917; 928 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Shadyside [912], 1918; 926 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Wireless-James L. Autry, Jr. [913], n.d.; 925 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - East Palestine Rubber Company [914], 1918-1919; 924 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Capital issues Committee of U.S. [915], 1918; 923 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Land Department - Drilling Leases [916], 1916; 922 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Republic Production Company - Production Reports [918A], 1916-1919; 921 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Republic Production Company-Misc. [918B], 1916-1917; 920 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Donations [919], 1918-1920; 919 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Coal Purchase for Autry Home [920], 1919; 918 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Autry's Summer Trip [922], 1919; 916 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Autry Genealogy [923], 1919-1920; 915 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Autry Genealogy [923], 1908-1930; 149037 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Papers re Galena-Signal Oil Merger [924], 1919; 914 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Y.W.C.A. Building Fund [925], 1919-1920; 913 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Autry Ranch Affairs [926], 1915-1920; 912 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Ex-Student's Association of the University of Texas [927], 1919; 911 (Box 22, Folder 1)
        General note
        (see also Founder's list Subscriptions Box 42 Folder 8)
      - A. Frost Justiss [928], 1919-1920; 910 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Purchase of Stutz Bearcat for James L. Autry Jr. [929], 1919; 909 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Expired Insurance Policies [930], 1917-1920; 908 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - First National Bank of Houston Stock [932], 1920; 906 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Autry Summer Trip [933], 1920; 905 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - California Trip [934], 1920; 904 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Fidelity Securities Company [935], 1919; 903 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Kent Place School for Allie May Autry [936], 1920; 902 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Carnegie Public Library, Houston [937], 1919-1920; 901 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Lot in Glenwood Cemetery [938], 1920; 900 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Home for Mrs. Alice Williams Crossland [939], 1920; 899 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Diocese of Dallas Endowment Fund [1090], 1897-1900; 895 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - United Sons of Confederate Veterans [1114], 1897-1898; 893 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Rental Contracts for Corsicana Property [1159], 1889-1898; 891 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Papers re Autry Purchase of Read & Jester Lots in Corsicana [1169], 1877-1899; 889 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Lou and James Carter Title Papers [1179], 1894-1900; 886 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Concerning the J.W. Moore Survey [1182], 1889-1899; 885 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Caradine Lands [1185], 1883-1888; 884 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous Deeds; List of Books Owned [1187], 1882-1897; 883 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Tax Receipts (Navarro, Polk, and Freestone Co.) [1189], 1878-1904; 882 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - Pecans - (correspondence with Sellers) [1409], 1900-1901; 1916-1918; 881 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - M. Autry Survey; Dispute Over Title [1443], 1877-1883; 880 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Mississippi Historical Society [1565], 1903; 879 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - American Historical Association [1566], 1902-1903; 878 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - Sun-Light Publishing Co. - Chas. A. Temple [1586], 1902-1903; 877 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - American Petroleum Company [2100], 1916; 875 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - Insurance: American Petroleum Company [2101], 1916; 874 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Accounting: American Petroleum Company [2102], 1916; 873 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Republic Production Company [2500], 1916; 872 (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - Accounting - Republic Production Company [2501], 1916; 871 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Sub-Series II: Legal Career, 1851-1920; 148775
      Numbered files pertaining to Autry's legal career beginning in 1881 under the apprenticeship of Beale up to and including his partnership with W.J. McKie.
      - Autry files, 1850-1919; 148833
        - Martin Palmer Papers, 1850; 148836 (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence - Legal Papers of Early Navarro County Clients, 1851-1903; 868 (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - R.C. Beale Law Licenses, 1867-1889; 148837 (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - Autry's Law License [1172], 1880-1887; 888 (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - T.S. Sweatman, Probate Court, 1868-1870; 148839 (Box 23, Folder 5)
        - Levi Jordon and L.A. Pettigrew deed, 1869-1870; 148840 (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - Gowan Papers, 1871-85; 148841 (Box 23, Folder 7)
        - R.C. Beale, Power of Attorney, 1874-1887; 148842 (Box 23, Folder 8)
        - M.M. and [M.] Walker, Bond, 1874; 148843 (Box 23, Folder 9)
        - Big Judge White, Will, 1875; 148844 (Box 23, Folder 10)
        - William Snow, Notarized Documents, 1877; 148845 (Box 23, Folder 11)
        - R.C. Beale, J.L. Harle Correspondence, 1880; 148846 (Box 23, Folder 12)
        - R.C. Beale and J. Autry Contract, 1881; 148847 (Box 23, Folder 13)
        - W.T. Vinns, Settlement of Estate, 1883; 148848 (Box 23, Folder 14)
        - R.C. Beale, H. Pillans Correspondence, 1884; 148849 (Box 23, Folder 15)
        - Henry Burrow, Receipt from Brown Estate, 1884; 148851 (Box 23, Folder 16)
        - Beale and Autry vs. Tom Mical, Citation and Judgment, 1885-86; 148852 (Box 23, Folder 17)
        - R.L. Brales, Assets, 1885; 148854 (Box 23, Folder 18)
        - Margaret Smith, Dave Ward, Bill of Sale and Lease, 1885; 148856 (Box 23, Folder 19)
        - S.J.T. Johnson and C.J. Hanson, memorandum of agreement, 1886; 148857 (Box 23, Folder 20)
        - Joe Stewart, Power of Attorney, 1886; 148858 (Box 23, Folder 21)
        - J.T. Luster Documents, 1887-88; 148860 (Box 23, Folder 22)
        - Robert Wilson Documents, 1887-93; 148861 (Box 23, Folder 23)
        - E.M. White and S.P. Cantrell, Promissory Note, 1887; 148863 (Box 23, Folder 24)
        - Corsicana Town Lot Company Charter, 1887; 148864 (Box 23, Folder 25)
        - Charles Giles Will, 1887; 148865 (Box 23, Folder 26)
        - A.B. Lee Affidavit, 1889; 148866 (Box 23, Folder 27)
        - Lane Family Receipt of Sale of Navarro County Property, 1889; 148867 (Box 23, Folder 28)
        - Gilbert Land Settlement [517A], 1895; 1252 (Box 23, Folder 29)
        - Mills et. al. v. Holloway [1605], 1895-1903; 876 (Box 23, Folder 30)
        - Goodwyn Estate [530], 1895-1909; 1215 (Box 23, Folder 31)
        - Correspondence - Port Arthur Land Company, 1901; 867 (Box 23, Folder 32)
        - Estate of Daniel Burke of Corsicana [583A], 1903-1910; 1135 (Box 23, Folder 33)
        - Correspondence between Autry & McKie [582A], 1903; 1138 (Box 23, Folder 34)
        - Correspondence between Autry & McKie [582A], 1903; 148876 (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence between Autry & McKie [582A], 1904; 1137 (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - Law Books [714], 1904-1915; 1077 (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - Cartwright Receivership Case (Cartwright et.al. v. Corsicana Water Co. et.al) [514], 1905; 1259 (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - Autry v. Fair [513], 1902-1906; 1261 (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - Brown v. McKie & Autry [502A], 1909-1911; 1277 (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - State v. Glass [584A], 1910-1911; 1134 (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Burrows v. Brown [538A], 1911; 1201 (Box 24, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence re: Will of Mrs. G. Mills [565A], 1912-1916; 1158 (Box 24, Folder 9)
        - Texas Abstract Co. v. Peck et.al. [723], 1914-1916; 1076 (Box 24, Folder 10)
        - Wills, Sundry [647], 1914-1916; 1093 (Box 24, Folder 11)
        - Texas Bar Assoc. Committee on Code of Professional Ethics [594], 1908-1909; 1126 (Box 24, Folder 12)
        - Houston Bar Association [514A], 1909-1912; 1258 (Box 24, Folder 13)
        - American Bar Association War Department Questionnaire, 1917; 148868 (Box 24, Folder 14)
        - Petroleum Refining Company of Texas Charter, 1918; 148869 (Box 24, Folder 15)
        - Corsicana Law Library Donation [921], 1919; 917 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Beale Estate, 1868-1921; 148834
        - M.E.V. Johnson v. Beale Estate [509], 1902-1910; 1268 (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - Beale Ranch [518A], 1910; 1250 (Box 25, Folder 2)
        - Beale Ranch [529], 1901-1906; 1221 (Box 25, Folder 3)
        - Blick Grant Henderson County (Beale Estate) [531A], 1872-1910; 1212 (Box 25, Folder 4)
        - Beale Estate [532A], 1908-1913; 1210 (Box 25, Folder 5)
        - Beale Ranch Matters [536], 1906; 1205 (Box 25, Folder 6)
        - Beale Estate - Polk Country Land; Mills v. Carter [542], 1893-1911; 1193 (Box 25, Folder 7)
        - Beale Estate - Polk County Land; Mills v. Walker [542], 1912-1913; 148877 (Box 25, Folder 8)
        - Beale Estate - Middleton Lands in Navarro County [544], 1896-1902; 1188 (Box 25, Folder 9)
        - Beale Ranch - 1907 [563], 1906-1908; 1162 (Box 25, Folder 10)
        - Barry Investments - Beale Estate [568], 1906-1909; 1155 (Box 26, Folder 1)
        - Barry Investments - Beale Estate [568], 1910-1914; 1154 (Box 26, Folder 2)
        - Beale Estate - Rental Contract Forms [575], 1916; 1146 (Box 26, Folder 3)
        - Beale Estate - T. H. Gerner Loan [578], 1904-1912; 1143 (Box 26, Folder 4)
        - Beale Ranch - 1908 Affairs [586], 1132 (Box 26, Folder 5)
        - Beale Estate Affairs [589A], 1914-1915; 1129 (Box 26, Folder 6)
        - Beale Ranch Affairs - 1909 [599], 1909-1910; 1117 (Box 26, Folder 7)
        - Beale Estate [778], 1915-1916; 1050 (Box 26, Folder 8)
        - Beale Estate Affairs [908], 1919-1921; 929 (Box 26, Folder 9)
        - Beale Estate Tripoli Mines [995], 1868-1893 Feb.; 898 (Box 26, Folder 10)
        - Beale Estate - Tripoli Mines [995], 1893 Mar.-1900; 897 (Box 26, Folder 11)
        - Beale Estate - Wise County Property [1005], 1895; 896 (Box 26, Folder 12)
        - Beale Estate - Taylor Place, Block K, Corsicana [1158], 1880-1894; 892 (Box 26, Folder 13)
        - Beale Estate - Corsicana Bakery Title Papers [1162], 1886-1896; 890 (Box 26, Folder 14)
        - Beale Estate - Claunch Place [1176], 1887-1888; 887 (Box 26, Folder 15)
        - Diary and ledger of R.C. Beale (photocopies from BEALE (R. CH.) PAPERS, 1872-1878, from the Briscoe Center for American History collection), 167421 (Box 26a, Folder 1-2)
      - Gates Estate, 1911-1918; 148835
        - John W. Gates Estate - Printed copies of will and petitions [524A], 1911-1912; 1236 (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - John W. Gates Estate - Inventory of Property [524A], 1911-1913; 1235 (Box 27, Folder 2)
        - John W. Gates Estate - Correspondence re: Payment of Inheritance Tax [524B], 1911-1913; 1234 (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - John W. Gates Estate - Petitions re: Payment of Inheritance Tax [524B], 1912; 1233 (Box 27, Folder 4)
        - John W. Gates Estate - Correspondence re: Probate of Will [524C], 1911; 1232 (Box 27, Folder 5)
        - John W. Gates Estate - Correspondence re: Probate of Will [524C], 1911-1912; 1231 (Box 27, Folder 6)
        - John W. Gates Estate - Correspondence re: Administration of Estate [524C], 1918; 1230 (Box 27, Folder 7)
        - Estate of Charles G. Gates [596A], 1913; 1120 (Box 27, Folder 8)
        - Estate of Charles G. Gates [596A], 1914-1915; 1119 (Box 28, Folder 1)
        - Thorburn v. Gates [783], 1916; 1045 (Box 28, Folder 2)
        - Surrogates' Court New York County. In the matter of the transfer tax upon the estate of John W. Gates deceased (2 folders), n.d.; 148893 (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
    - Sub-Series III: Business Papers, 1851-1913; 835
      This sub-series contains numbered files pertaining to The Texas Company and correspondence regarding Autry's other business interests. Autry's files on American Republics Corporation, Fidelity Trust Company, Mexico Fuel Company, and Texas Land & Abstract Company can be found in the Numbered Files series. An example of the business files of importance is the correspondence between McKie and Autry while they were still partners and representing the Texas Fuel Company. Also there are files related to Autry's resignation from the Texas Company with personal letters from friends commenting on his actions. Correspondence with Autry's other business partners: J.S. Cullinan and Will C. Hogg is also included.
      - The Texas Company, 1901-1920; 851
        - Correspondence -The Texas Company - Legal, 1902-1903; 866 (Box 29, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence - The Texas Company - Legal, 1904; 865 (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence - The Texas Company - Legal, 1905; 864 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence - The Texas Company - Legal, 1906; 863 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence - The Texas Company - Legal, 1907; 862 (Box 29, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence - The Texas Company - Legal, 1911; 861 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence - The Texas company - Legal, 1912; 860 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - Texas Company Stock Matters, Personal [501A], 1905-1914; 1278 (Box 30, Folder 1)
        - Hall - Bailey Accusations Matter [554A], 1907-1909; 1175 (Box 30, Folder 2)
        - Strattleman v. Cullinan [563A], 1912; 1161 (Box 30, Folder 3)
        - Attorney General's Investigation [571A], 1909-1913; 1149 (Box 30, Folder 4)
        - Donation of Sharswood's Legal Ethics [589], 1908; 1130 (Box 30, Folder 5)
        - The Texas Co. (Ancient History, Clippings, etc.) [590A], 1902; 1128 (Box 30, Folder 6)
        - The Texas Co. - Miscellaneous [609], 1914; 1114 (Box 30, Folder 7)
        - J.R. Sharp Litigation [616], 1913-1914; 1112 (Box 30, Folder 8)
        - The Texas Company - Early Papers [619A], 1901-1902; 1109 (Box 30, Folder 9)
        - The Texas Company - Cullinan & Autry Resignation [619], 1912-1913; 1110 (Box 30, Folder 10)
        - Cullinan v. Sterling [660], 1914; 1089 (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - The Texas Co. - Internal Affairs [727], 1915; 1073 (Box 31, Folder 2)
        - The Texas Co. -70,000 Share Stock Issue [740], 1915; 1068 (Box 31, Folder 3)
        - Autry Sale of Texas Company Stock [753], 1915; 1065 (Box 31, Folder 4)
        - Estate of W.B. Sharp [785], 1913-1919; 1044 (Box 31, Folder 5)
        - The Texas Company - Credit Balances [884], 1916; 951 (Box 31, Folder 6)
        - The Texas Company - Statement [885], 1916; 950 (Box 31, Folder 7)
        - The Texas Company [from exhibit at Texas State Fair 1908], 1902-1907; 148991 (Box 31, Folder 8)
        - Photocopy of Check to Jas. L. Autry from the Texas Company, 1903 May 15; 648; DS (Box 31, Folder 9)
        - Texas Court of Civil Appeals - Brief, Texas Co. v. D.W. Strange, n.d.; 859 (Box 31, Folder 10)
        - District Court Abstract, Acadia Parish, La. "Houssiere - Latreille" Cases, n.d.; 858 (Box 31, Folder 11)
        - Supreme Court of Louisiana, Jennings-Heywood Oil Syndicate v. HoussiereLatreille Oil Co., et. al., vol. I, II, 857 (Box 31, Folder 12)
        - Supreme Court of Louisiana, Reply to Brief - Houissiere-Latreille Oil Co. v. Jennings Heywood Oil Syndicate, 856 (Box 31, Folder 13)
        - Supreme Court of Louisiana, Brief - Caddo Oil and Mining Company v. Producers Oil Company, 855 (Box 31, Folder 14)
        - Texas Court of Civil Appeals, Brief - Lena Bender, et. al. v. R.E. Brooks et. al., 854 (Box 31, Folder 15)
        - Supreme Court of Oklahoma, Brief - State of Oklahoma and Jim Crow Oil Company v. Larry Nolegs et. al., 853 (Box 31, Folder 16)
        - General Corporation Laws of the State of Delaware, n.d.; 852 (Box 31, Folder 17)
        - Trial balances, 1918; 153201 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Business Correspondence, 148942
        - J.S. Cullinan [632], 1905-1914; 1103 (Box 32, Folder 1)
        - J.S. Cullinan [633], 1915-1920; 1102 (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - J.S. Cullinan [789], 1914-1919; 1040 (Box 32, Folder 3)
        - W.C. Hogg [634], 1913-1919; 1101 (Box 32, Folder 4)
        - W.C. Hogg [815], 1914-1919; 1018 (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - E.E. Clark, 1919; 148957 (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondents, 1915-1920; 148958 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Acknowledgement of the loss of the Honorable Jas. L. Autry from the Board of Directors of the American Republics Corporation, October 20, 1920; 148995 (Drawer 81)
      - Agreement of Feb. 23, 1918; transcript, 1918 Feb.23; 870 (Box 33)
    - Sub-Series IV: Personal, 1869-1992, 148785
      This sub-series contains correspondence between family members and friends; numbered files referring to Autry's personal residences (Corsicana, Beaumont, and Courtlandt Place in Houston); family genealogy; photographs, clippings, memorabilia, and Autry family histories.
      - Personal Correspondence, 1869-1920, 815
        - R.L. Watson to James L. Autry, 1869 Aug. 5; 692; ALS (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - James L. Autry to Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry, Dec 13, 1873; 678; ALS (Box 34, Folder 2)
        - James L. Autry To Mrs. Jeanie V. Brown, January 16, 1879; 149747 (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - John Young Gooch to James L. Autry, 1880 Nov. 11; 674; ALS (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - C.R. Gibson to James L. Autry, 1880 Nov. 17; 673; ALS (Box 34, Folder 5)
        - George P. Finlay to James L. Autry, 1880 Nov. 17; 672; ALS (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - John D. Templeton to James L. Autry, 1880 Nov. 18; 671; ALS (Box 34, Folder 7)
        - John H. Cochran to James L. Autry, 1880 Nov. 18; 670; ALS (Box 34, Folder 8)
        - R.C. Foster to James L. Autry, 1880 Nov. 19; 669; ALS (Box 34, Folder 9)
        - B.M. Baker to James L. Autry, 1880 Nov. 22; 668; ALS (Box 34, Folder 10)
        - W.F. Upton to James L. Autry, 1880 Nov. 22; 667; ALS (Box 34, Folder 11)
        - Grewett Goodson to James L. Autry, 1880 Dec. 3; 666; ALS (Box 34, Folder 12)
        - G.R. Reeve to James L. Autry, 1880 Dec. 9; 664; ALS (Box 34, Folder 13)
        - G.R. Reeves to James L. Autry, 1880 Dec. 16; 661; APS (Box 34, Folder 14)
        - R.C. Saunders to Jas. L. Autry, 1880 Dec. 16; 660; ALS (Box 34, Folder 15)
        - R.C. Beale to James L. Autry, 1881 Jan. 6; 657; ALS (Box 34, Folder 16)
        - R.C. Beale to James L. Autry, 1881 Feb. 4; 656; ALS (Box 34, Folder 17)
        - R.C. Beale to James L. Autry, 1881 Feb. 14; 653; ALS (Box 34, Folder 18)
        - John D. Lee to James L. Autry, 1881 Feb. 22; 652; ALS (Box 34, Folder 19)
        - R.C. Beale to James L. Autry, 1881 Feb. 24; 651; ALS (Box 34, Folder 20)
        - St. John's Church, Corsicana, 1893-1910; 834 (Box 34, Folder 21)
        - James L. Autry to Christ Church, 1907-1913; 829 (Box 34, Folder 22)
        - James L. Autry to Jeanie V. Brown, 1908-1911; 618 (Box 34, Folder 23)
        - James L. Autry to Allie Autry, 1910-1911; 607 (Box 34, Folder 24)
        - James L. Autry to Allie Autry, 1912; 604 (Box 34, Folder 25)
        - Various Friends to James L. Autry, 1914-1920; 148996 (Box 34, Folder 26)
        - James L. Autry to Fred W. Freeman, 1914; 821 (Box 34, Folder 27)
        - James M. Greer to James L. Autry, 1915-1918; 149001 (Box 34, Folder 28)
        - James L. Autry to Allie Autry, 1916; 598 (Box 34, Folder 29)
        - James L. Autry to Allie Autry, 1917; 594 (Box 34, Folder 30)
        - James L. Autry, Jr. to Jeanie V. Brown, n.d.; 593 (Box 34, Folder 31)
        - C. Cotton to J.L. Autry, n.d.; 645; ALS (Box 34, Folder 31)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1900-1904; 833 (Box 34, Folder 32)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1905; 832 (Box 34, Folder 33)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1906; 831 (Box 35, Folder 1)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1907; 830 (Box 35, Folder 2)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1908; 828 (Box 35, Folder 3)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1909; 827 (Box 35, Folder 4)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1910; 826 (Box 35, Folder 5)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1911; 825 (Box 35, Folder 6)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1912; 824 (Box 35, Folder 7)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1913; 823 (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1914; 822 (Box 36, Folder 2)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1915; 820 (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1916-1917; 819 (Box 36, Folder 4)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1918; 818 (Box 36, Folder 5)
        - Personal Correspondence, 1919-1920; 817 (Box 36, Folder 6)
        - Personal Correspondence, 816 (Box 36, Folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous Autry notes, n.d.; 636 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Personal Financial Records, 1881-1919; 149008
        - James L. Autry - Blank Debit Voucher Pad, 156811 (Box 37, Folder 1)
        - Tax Matters - Personal Property [517], 1905-1915; 1253 (Box 37, Folder 2)
        - Coahoma Trust for Mrs. Jeannie Brown [527], 1905-1912; 1225 (Box 37, Folder 3)
        - Personal Cash Accounts [556A], 1912-1914; 1174 (Box 37, Folder 4)
        - Personal Financial Affairs [596], 1904-1909; 1124 (Box 37, Folder 5)
        - Personal Financial Affairs [596], 1910; 1123 (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - Personal Financial Affairs [596], 1911; 1122 (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - Personal Financial Affairs [596], 1912-1914; 1121 (Box 37, Folder 8)
        - Autry Financial [713], 1914-1915; 1078 (Box 37, Folder 9)
        - Mother's Trust [803], 1916; 1029 (Box 37, Folder 10)
        - Personal Taxes [810], 1906-1920; 1022 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - Autry Income Tax [824], 1915-1920; 1009 (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - Memo of Bank Balances, 1915-1920; 156906 (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - Personal Taxes [827], 1916-1920; 1007 (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Personal Financial Statement [863], 1881-1912; 972 (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - Autry personal Finances [931], 1919-1920; 907 (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - Investment Data, 1919; 149005 (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - Trial balance, 1919-20; 149048 (Box 38, Folder 8)
        - James L. Autry - Check Register, Personal Accounts, July 2, 1910-December 31, 1915; 525 (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - James L. Autry - Ledger, 1896-1898; 532 (Box 39, Folder 2)